Irving P. Krick papers, 1921-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Weather Modification Project
  - Local prospect: Oregon (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Oklahoma, Ferdie Dearing correspondence (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Active client: California (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Active client: New Mexico (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (1 of 3) (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (2 of 3) (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (3 of 3) (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: New Mexico (1 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: New Mexico (2 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Texas (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Africa (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Afghanistan (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (1 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (2 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (1 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Oklahoma, Stillwater project (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Oklahoma, miscellaneous projects (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Alberta Crop Insurance Corporation (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Operations (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Active client: Weston County Weather Research Association (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Active client: Converse County Weather Research Corporation, Wyoming (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Active client: Goshen County Weather Research Inc, Wyoming (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Wyoming Weather Inc. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Laramie County Weather Inc., Wyoming (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Wyo-Braska Weather Inc., Nebraska (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Apple Weather Inc, Washington (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - National Weather Modification Policies and Programs (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Active client: U.S. Air Force (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous articles and papers on weather modification (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Active client: Alberta Ground Generator Preliminary Report (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Hail and thunderstorms research (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Cotton County, Oklahoma (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: California, smog (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: California, smog (2 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Active client: Oklahoma Publishing Company (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Colorado River (1 of 3) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Colorado River (2 of 3) (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: Colorado River (3 of 3) (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Kansas (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Kansas (2 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Kneehill, Alberta - Jim Bishop (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Kneehill, Alberta - Jim Bishop (2 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Kneehill, Alberta - Jim Bishop (1 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Kneehill, Alberta - Jim Bishop (2 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Alberta Hail Studies, Research Council (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Final report: Alberta Ground Generator Study (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Oklahoma (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Active client: Alberta Research Council (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Alberta (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Active client: Alberta Research Council (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Alberta Weather Modification Association (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Unifarm, Alberta (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Alberta (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Ohio (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: France (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Weather Service Orders (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Foreign prospects: Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Medford Pear Shippers' Association, Oregon (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Red River Valley Water Resources Association, Louisiana (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Active client: Sacramento River Weather Association, California (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Contracts: E.R. McDonald and Sons, Louisiana (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Active client: E.R. McDonald and Sons, Louisiana (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Oklahoma State University of Agriculture (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Oklahoma State University of Agriculture (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Sherman Cooperative Grain Growers (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Crop Protection Incorporated, Oregon (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Crop Protection Incorporated, Oregon (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Morrow County Weather Research Association, Oklahoma (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Morrow County Weather Research Association, Oklahoma (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Active client: Woodward County Cloud Seeding Association, Oklahoma (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Active client: Harper County Weather Incorporated, Oklahoma (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Active client: Vandalia Civic Advancement Association, Illinois (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Active client: Shreveport, Department of Water and Sewage, Louisiana (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Placer County Farm Labor Cooperative, California (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Pacific Power and light Co., Oregon (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Grant County, South Dakota (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Weather Modification Cooperative Limited, Alberta (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Department of Lighting, Seattle, Washington (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Rain Seekers Inc., Michigan (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: I-Card Inc., Michigan (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Barry Weather Inc., Michigan (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Client reports: Public Service Commission, Wisconsin (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Client reports: Michigan Weather Inc. (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Client reports: South Central Michigan Weather Modification Association (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Generators: ARC Model (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Generators: Belts (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Generators: Chemical companies (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Generators: Fuel costs (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Generators: Model 15 Fire Tubes (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Equipment: Connectors equipment (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Generators: Malinckrodt Chemicals, Canada (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Generators: Eastern Smelting and Refining Corps, Massachussetts (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Generators: Deepwater Chemical Co., California (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Generators: Commercial Solvents Corp., Louisiana (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Generators: Carbon rods (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Generators: Static meter, non-directional (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Generators: Static meter, directional (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Generators: Nuclei counter, portable (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Generators: Coke Model 15 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Generators: Coke crusher (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Final report: Alberta Research Council (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Operation maps: Alberta (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Operation maps: New Mexico, Texas (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Operation maps: Oklahoma (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Plume worksheet (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Radiosonde data sheets, Fort Sill, Oklahoma (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Convective potential checklist: Southwest Cooperative Program, Oklahoma (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Active client: Red Bluff Power Control District, Texas (1 of 3) (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Active client: Red Bluff Power Control District, Texas (2 of 3) (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Active client: Red Bluff Power Control District, Texas (3 of 3) (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Final report: M-Card Inc., Michigan (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Final report: M-Card Inc., Michigan (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Final report: M-Card Inc., I-Card Inc., Michigan (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Final report: Delaware Weather Modification Program Inc. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Final report: Grand Mesa Water Users Association, Colorado (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Final report: City of Lawton, Oklahoma (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Final report: Diamond A Cattle Company, New Mexico (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Final report: Tequesquite Ranch, New Mexico (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Final report: Gratriot, Isabella, Montcalm counties, North Dakota (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Natchitoches Parish, Louisiana (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Final report: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Final report: Concordia Water Resources Development Corp., Louisiana (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Final report: Natchitoches Parish, Louisiana (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Final report: IAMO Weather Modification Corp., Missouri (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Maps for report, Delaware (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Final report: Weather Control Cloud Modification Commission, New Mexico (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Final report: I-Card Inc., Michigan (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Final report: Upper Peninsula Weather Agricultural Research, Michigan (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Final report: Big Stone Weather Inc., Minnesota (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Final report: Central Minnesota Weather Inc. (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Final report: M-Card Inc., I-Card Inc., Mihcigan (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Active client: Courtright Cattle Co., Washington (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Final report: Southwestern Michigan (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Final report: Gratiot County Weather Modification Ltd., Michigan (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Final report: Louisiana Department of Agriculture (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Client reports: Minnesota Weather Inc. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Natchitoches Parish Water Committee Inc., Louisiana (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: Louisiana Water Resources Corp. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (1 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (2 of 2) (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: Department of Water Utilities, Louisiana (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Texas operation plans and permit applications (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Oklahoma permit applications (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Canadian forms (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Service order forms for weather modification operations (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Generator operations forms and instructions (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Generator report forms, Colorado (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Client reprots: Adams County Weather Modification Corp., Iowa (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Client reports: Northwester Oklahoma projects (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Final report: Henry C. Hitch Ranch Inc., Oklahoma (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Final reprot: Henry C. Hitch Ranch Inc., Oklahoma (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Final report: Oklahoma Farm and Ranch Areas (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Final report: Hitch ARGI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Final report: Hitch ARGI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Final report: Hitch ARGI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - A Weather Engineering Proposal, by Krick (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Weather Modification Proposal for Edwards underground Water District (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Weather Modification Proposals for Alberta (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Final report: Ground Generator Assessment, Alberta Research Council (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Engineering report: Study of Cloud Seeding Potentialities to Increase Natural Precipitation for Queensland, Australia (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Canada, Supplement (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - The Feasibility of Commercialization of Long Range Weather Forecasts... Vol. 1 and 2, U.S. Department of Energy (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Various research papers (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Excerpt from Encyclopedia of American History (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Various indices (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Preliminary report: Alberta Ground Generator Study (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Various charts and tables, Alberta, Canada (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Various research papers (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Annual Review of Weather Modification Activities in California, Oct 1, 1977 to Sep 20, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Research Council of Alberta: Meeting minutes (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Paper: Hailstorm Research at McGill University (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Various research papers (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Edwards Underground Water District (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Fergus Wood proposal (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous prospects (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Various Oklahoma reports and correspondence (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Australia (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: TSI, Inc., Washington (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Various prospects and correspondence (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Various prospects (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Jim Bishop presentation (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Various prospects (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Active client: Australia (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Engineering report: Queensland, Australia (Draft) (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Drafts and letters to utility companies (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Proposal: Australia (draft) (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Various prospects (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Active client: Oklahoma (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Alberta, Canada (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Via Computers Inc (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Stags Leap, CA (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Stags Leap, CA (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Northeast (Delaware, Maryland) (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Northeast (Delaware, Maryland) (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Grand Mesa Water Users, Colorado (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Kansas (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Iowa (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Active client: Minnesota (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Active client: Menominee County, Michigan (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, correspondence with Ferdie Deering (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Colorado (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Active client: Texas (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Active client: Texas (2 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, Statewide programs (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: South America (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Utah (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Washington (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, correspondence with Ferdie Deering (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Foreign prospect: Guadalupe, French West Indies (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Foreign prospect: France (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Foreign prospect: West Indies (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Weather predictions for March 1947 in Denver, Colorado (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Iran (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Gratiot, Michigan (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Active client: South Dakota (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Foreign prospect: Brazil (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Foreign prospect: Canary Islands (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Nebraska (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Foreign prospect: Puerto Rico (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Oregon (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma, news clippings (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Lebanon (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Libya (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Foreign prospect: Argentina (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Maps: Iowa and Oklahoma (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Hawaii (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Deparrtment of Agriculture (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., District of Columbia (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Massachusetts, Department of the Air Force (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Texas (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., White House (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Miscellaneous government agencies (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: Michigan (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Ski tows, various states (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: Georgia (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: Delaware (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Florida (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Local prospect: California (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Local prospect: Nevada (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Local prospect: Nebraska (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Foreign prospect: Yugoslavia (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Foreign prospect: South Africa (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Foreign prospect: Hungary (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Local prospect: Various (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Foreign prospect: India (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Foreign prospect: India (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: California, U.S. Department of the Navy (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: India (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Colorado River Project, historical and political information (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Foreign prospect: Venezuela (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Canada: Supplement (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Canada: Quebec supplement (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Western Canada (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Western Canada (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Eastern Canada (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Record Meteorological Observations in Western Canada (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - National Weather Service: A Strategy and Organization Concept for the Future (1 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - National Weather Service: A Strategy and Organization Concept for the Future (2 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - WMA: The Journal of Weather Modification, Vol. 6, No. 1 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - WMA: The Journal of Weather Modification, Vol. 7, No. 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Engineering Report: Cloud Seeding Potentialities for Queensland (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Final report: Tequesquite Ranch, New Mexico (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Final report: City of Lawton, Oklahoma (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Final report: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Final report: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Final report: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Final report: Gratiot County, Michigan (M-Card and I-Card Inc.) (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Delaware Weather Modification Program Inc. (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Final report: Grand Mesa Water Users Association, Colorado (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Final report: Upper Peninsula Weather Agriculture Research Development, Michigan (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Final report: IAMO Weather Modification Corp, Iowa (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Final report: Department of Agriculture, Louisiana (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Final report: Southwestern Michigan (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Final report: Concordia Water Resource Development Corp., Louisiana (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Final report: Natchitoches Parish Water Committee Inc., Louisiana (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Final report: Central Minnesota Weather Inc. (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Final report: Diamond A Cattle Co., New Mexico (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - A Summary of Rain Increase Operations, Central Michigan, 1972-74 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Preliminary Report of Cloud Seeing Operations, Eastern Washington (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Petition to Establish the Viticultural Area of "Stag's Leap" (1 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Petition to Establish the Viticultural Area of "Stag's Leap" (2 of 2) (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Alberta Ground Generator Study, Case Studies and Conclusions (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Proposal: Australia (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: Toole County Rural Development Corp., Montana (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Toole County Rural Development Corp., Montana (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: Weather Modification Association of Branch County, Michigan (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Tri-Counties Rural development Association, Montana (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Client reports: Arbuckle Weather Modification District, Oklahoma (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Client reports: Kiowa County Weather Modification Association, Oklahoma (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Final report: Comanche County Weather Modification Inc., Oklahoma (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Final report: Comanche County Weather Moditication Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Final report: Comanche County Weather Modification Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Final report: Comanche County Weather Modification Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Final report: Weather Modification Inc., Texas (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Orders: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Orders: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Orders: Comanche County Weather Modification Inc., Oklahoma (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Orders: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Orders: Sacramento Department of Water Resources, California (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Orders: Oklahoma State University (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Orders: Brown Ranch, Texas (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Orders: Alberta Research Council (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Generator operators: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Final report: Department of Natural Resources, Washington (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Orders: Kiowa County Weather Modification Association, Oklahoma (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Orders: Natchitoches Parish Water Committee, Louisiana (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Generator operators: Oklahoma (OC-12) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Generator operators: Hitch AGRI-Business Inc., Oklahoma (OC-4) (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Generator operators: Oklahoma (OC-16) (1 of 2) (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Generator operators: Oklahoma (OC-16) (2 of 2) (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Generator operators: Oklahoma (OC-3) (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Generator operators: Louisiana (LA-9) (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Generator operators: Alberta (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Generator operators: Texas (T-17) (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Michigan (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - NOAA: Initial reports, Oklahoma (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Oklahoma (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Texas and Oklahoma (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Arkansas (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Lawton, Oklahoma (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - NOAA: Final reports, Michigan (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - NOAA: Final reports, California (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous weather maps (1 of 2) (Box 104, Folder 9)